>> Kyle Simpson: 最后，让我们看看 ToBoolean 抽象操作。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And finally, let's look
at the ToBoolean abstract operation.
顺便说下，这四个是我们所看到的，两个原始，两个字符串，
And by the way, these four are what we're
looking at, two primitive, two string,
两个数字和两个布尔值。
two number, and two Boolean.
还存在其他引用和使用的抽象操作。
There are other abstract operations
that they refer to and use.
所以如果你好奇的话就读这些规范
So read those in the spec
if you're curious, but
这些是你要做的主要的
these are the major ones
you're gonna run into.
因此，在该规范中， " ToBoolean" 第 7.1.2 节。
So ToBoolean, section 7.1.2 in the spec.
任何时候都有任何不是布尔值的值，并且
Anytime you have any value
that is not a Boolean, and
它是在一个需要一个布尔型的地方使用的。
it's used in a place that needs a Boolean,
this operation occurs.
和其他的完全一样好吗
Exactly the same as the other ones, okay?
此操作较少算法和更多查找。
This operation is less algorithmic and
more lookup.
除了说这个值之外还有别的事情要做
There's not really anything to do,
other than to say, is the value,
我们所谓的谬误，或者不是，这才是唯一的问题。
what we call falsy, or not,
that's really the only question here.
所以基本上有一个查找表。
So there's essentially a look up table.
这个字号的字面上说，这里就是其中一个的价值
Literally in the spec, that says, here is
the value of one of these things if so
返回 false，表示 false 值是从 ToBoolean 返回的值。
return false, meaning the false value
is what came back from ToBoolean.
否则就回到现实吧
And otherwise just return true.
因此，它定义了一个我们称为 " 谬误值" 的非常具体的和简短的有限列表。
So it defines a very specific and short
limited list of what we call falsy values.
这是当强制使用布尔值时将返回 false 的值，
That is values that will return
false when coerced to a Boolean,
以及任何可以将其胁迫为布尔值的方法。
and any of the various ways that
you can coerce to a Boolean.
这些都是谬误的价值观。
These are the falsy values.
空字符串，为 0， null， NaN， false和
The empty string, either of the 0,
the null, the NaN, the false, and
未定义。
the undefined.
这些都是我们的谬论。
Those are our falsy values.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 如果不在名单上，它永远是真实的，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If it's not on that list,
it is always truthy, okay?
如果不在名单上就好了
If it's not on the list, it is truthy.
这个列表上的一些例子是无限长的。
So some examples of things on that list,
that list is infinitely long.
但有些例子是一串字符串
But some examples would be a string,
数字，对象，数组， true，函数。
a number, an object,
an array, true, function.
这些都是真实的价值观。
Those are all truthy values.
让我们看看你是否在关注
Let's see if you're paying attention.
如果尝试两个布尔值为空数组，那么会发生什么情况 ?
What would happen if you try
to two Boolean an empty array?
这会是真的吗还是假的
Would it be truthy or would it be falsy?
非常关注我对 ToBoolean的描述
So pay very close attention to
how I describe to ToBoolean,
它不调用这两种基本算法。
it does not invoke the two
primitive algorithm.
或者这两个数字，或者这个字符串，或者任何东西，它只会查一查。
Or the two number, or the to string,
or anything, it just does a look up.
那么名单上的空行是空话吗 ?
So is the empty array
on the falsy the list?
>> class: 否。
&gt;&gt; class: No.
>> Kyle Simpson: 那么它必须返回什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what must it return?
>> class: Truthy。
&gt;&gt; class: Truthy.
>> Kyle Simpson: True，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: True, okay?
那是你对 Booleans 做决定的关键
That's a key thing to keep in your
mind when you're doing to Booleans,
当事情发生的时候就没有其他的胁迫的事情发生了
when that's what's happening,
there's no other coercion stuff happening.
这只是个直说的问题，是有还是没有。
It's just a straight look up,
is it there or is it not.
不能将值覆盖为字符串或任何内容。
You can't override it with a value
over to string or anything.
只是在名单上还是不在名单上
It's just is it on the list or
is it not, okay?
这就是我们如何得到我们的谬误和真实价值的。
So that's how we get our falsy and
truthy values.
本质上记住名单上的谬误
Essentially, memorize the falsy the list,
and
那么总是问下那个名单上的价值如果是那么虚假的话，否则它必须是真实的。
then always ask is the value on that list
if so falsy, otherwise, it must be truthy.